인생에서 소중한 것들은 공짜라고
best things in life are free.
그래, 내가 좀 많이 뺏어먹긴 하네
Okay, you're right. I eat your food a lot.
이러면 어떨까?
Now, how about this?
우리 집 냉장고를 맘껏 쓰도록 해
You can raid my fridge anytime you want.
엄청난 배려군
Oh, that's very kind of you.
D셀 배터리 전해질로
Next time I have a hankering to wash down a D-cell battery
오래 묵은 피클 주스가 필요할 때
with a jar of old pickle juice,
한번 들리지 뭐
(clicks tongue) I'll come a-knockin'.
라지, 답변은 언제 받을 수 있을까
Hey, Raj, you didn't send your RSVP in.
결혼식에 같이 올 사람 있어?
I'm suppose to ask you if you're bringing someone to the wedding.
다음에 알려줄게
I'll let you know.
최대한 빨리 알려줄 수 있어?
Well, can you make it soon?
자리 배치 문제로 양쪽에서 싸우고 있어
There's a battle royale going on over the seating charts.
한쪽 코너는 장모님, 나머지 셋은 엄마가 차지했어
In one corner, Bernadette's mom, in the other three, mine.